Guide to the Jacob Herbert Bruckner papers, 1938-1968.
Bruckner, Jacob Herbert papers, 1938-1968.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jacob Herbert Bruckner papers, 1938-1968.
21-31-1326
Jacob Herbert Bruckner, 1905-1970.
12 cubic ft.
Movie film, film strips, slides, patents, professional journals, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes material on animal and poultry societies.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
J. Herbert Bruckner was a professor of poultry science at the Cornell University College of Agriculture, and was chairman of the department from 1940-1965.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes material on animal and poultry societies; professional organizations; faculty, students, and various committees at Cornell University; movie film, film strips, and slides; patents; professional journals; and correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bruckner, Jacob Herbert, 1905-1970.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
Subjects:
Poultry--Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Motion pictures.; Patents (license).; Slides (photographs).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Subject files, A-Z
  - A
    - Correspondence, 1952- (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AAUP (American Association of University Professors) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Address of Agricultual Experiment Stations (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Administration, 1952- (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Administration - Cornell (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Science Youth Program, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alfred - Agricultural and Technical Institute (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - John B. Allred (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Poultry Association, 1956- (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Poultry Historical Society; Secretary, Paul Sanford (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Poultry Historical Society, 1956- (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Poultry Historical Society (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Animal Welfare League, 1962- (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Ash, W.J., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Ash, W.J., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Ash, William J., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ash, William J., 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Awards, 1956- (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - B
    - Correspondence, 1956- (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Babcock's Hatchery, 1952- (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Robert F. Ball, 1952- (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Beacon Milling Company, 1952- (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bearse, Gordon, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bearse, Gordon, 1941-1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Biological Science Division (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Botsford, H.E. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Max M. Brender, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Buildings and Properties, maintenance (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Buildings and Properties (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - C
    - Correspondence, 1954- (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - C. and R. Duck Farm, 1957- (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Jim Carson, 1942- (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Centennial Report, Department of Poultry Husbandry (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Chick Master Incubator Company, Plus Chick Sex Manual, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Cornell Poultry Pointers - pamphlets (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cole (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - College Feed Service (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - College Fleet (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Poultry Course Work (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Committee, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - College of Agriculture, Ideas for the Future (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Committee: Biometry and Statistics, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Committee: Admissions (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Curriculum Committee, N.Y.S. College of Agriculture, Ad Hoc (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Ad Hoc Committee #3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Eductional Program (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Committee Bio. Sci. (Corson) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Department of Development (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Committee of Extension (Bauckmen Comm.), 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Committee Extension (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Committee, Food Technology, 1955- (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Long Range Planning, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Committee, Honors Program (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Membership University Faculty (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Committee, Patent and Trademark (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Committee, Revision of Calendar (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Biology, President's (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Committee, Relationship to State Institutes, 1955- (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Committee, General Laboratory, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - H.E. Cushman (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Courses, Poultry, Registration, Proposed Curriculum, 1954- (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - D
    - Correspondence, 1954- (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - L.B. Darrah, 1949- (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bruce, R. Davisson, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Directory, former undergrad students (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Doolittle, Donald Preston (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Doolittle, Donald P. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - E
    - Eggs, colored (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Egg Laying Tests, Historical (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Egg I-Q Program, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence E, 1954- (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Embrology of the Chick: List of References (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Expense Account, J.H. Bruckner (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - F
    - General Legislation of the University Faculty and Extracts from its Records - 2 pamphlets; Faculty Handbook - 1, 1954- (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence F, 1954- (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Faculty, Agr. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Faculty University, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Faculty, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Faculty, 1963-1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Faculty, 1960-1961; 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Faculty, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Faculty, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Farms Available (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Feathers (M.L. Hurd), Oct. 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - W.T. Federer, 1958- (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 19660 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Visitors (foreign), 1961- (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Fox, Thomas W. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Fraternity (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - French, O.C., 1956- (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - G
    - Game Birds (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - G.L.F. Research (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - G.L.F. - Farm Testing, 1955- (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, G, 1954- (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - R.S. Gowe, 1956- (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Grades, 1961- (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Grades, 1957; 1959,; 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Graduate School, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Graduate School, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Graduate School, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Graduate School, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Graduate Work in the Poultry Sciences (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Graduate School (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Graduate School, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Graduate School, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Graduate School, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Student Courses, Spring Term, 1957- (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Former Graduate Student, Paul Lague (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Former Graduate Student, Mario M. Labadan (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Former Graduate Student, Sergio Rojas (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Former Graduate Student, Gad Zeitlin (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Abstracts of Theses Departmental (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Graduate Student, Misc., 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - H
    - Correspondence, 19554- (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - History, Department (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - G.O. Hall, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - L.H. Harden, 1955- (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Heads of Poultry Departments in Other Colleges (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Heads of Departments, N.Y.S. College of Agriculture (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Hertel, J.P., Resident Instruction, Roberts Hall (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - G.F. Heuser, 1946- (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - G.F. Heuser, 1938-1945 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - High School Science Program, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - High School Natural Science, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - High School National Science, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - High School Natural Science Program, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - High School Natural Science Program (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - F.W. Hill, 1957- (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - F.W. Hill, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hogsett Poultry Ranch, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - John H. Holser, 1942-1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Honors Program (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - C.E. Howes (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - L.M. Hurd, 1938- (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - J.C. Huttar, 1956- (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - H.C. Hutchings, Jr., 1953- (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - I
    - Correspondence, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - International Agricultural Development (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - International Baby Chick Association, 1942- (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Intergration (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - J
    - Correspondence, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Johndrew, Egg Mkt. Inst., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Jungle Fowl (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - K
    - Steven C. King, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence K, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Irving J. Kauder (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Kellogg Foundation, W.K., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - L
    - Land Holdings (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Legislation, 1935- (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - W.F. Lamoreux, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence L, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - P.P. Levine, 1945- (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Library, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Lights (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Jack Long, 1951- (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Mac and Mc
    - Correspondence, Mac and Mc, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - F.L. McCarthney, 1943- (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - C.M. McCay, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lloyd A. McDonald (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Dewey McNiece, 1953- (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - R.J. McVicker, 1955- (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - M
    - Correspondence M, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Marble (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Manuscript, D.R. Marble (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - J. Holmes Martin, 1941- (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Massachusettes Breeders' School, 1946- (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Robert B. Meigs, 1955- (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - W.J. Mellen, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Frank Millarch, 1960- (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Moving Picture Film and Film Strips, 7 slides, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - R.A. Monroe, 1956- (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Morgan (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - N
    - Correspondence N, 1954- (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Nakashima (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - National Institute of Animal Agriculture, 1951- (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - National Poultry Advisory Council, 1944- (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - National Poultry Improvement Plan, Graphs and Charts, 1944- (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - National Poultry Improvement Plan, U.S.D.A., 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - National Poultry Improvement Plan, 1940- (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - NEPPCO, 1954- (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Nesheim, M.C. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Newcastle Disease (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council, 1954- (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council, L.M. Hurd (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - N.Y.S. Baby Chick Association, 1954- (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - New York Hatchery Association (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Advisory Committee, 1949- (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Chest, 1949- (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council (old) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - N.Y.S. Pullorum Control, 1956- (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - N.Y.S. Turkey Growers and Turkey News, 1955- (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - L.C. Norris, 1954- (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - L.C. Norris, 1942-1953 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - School of Nutrition, 1942- (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - O
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Office Memorandums (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Ogle, R.C., 1949- (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - P
    - Correspondence P, 1954- (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Patents, 1957- (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - R.W. Patten, 1945- (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - L.F. Payne, 1942-1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Copy: JHB, 39:11 Geographic Variation and Sub-Species in the Genus Phasianus (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Pheasants, Research (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Publications (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Pheasants, Albino (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pheasants, General (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Personnel (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - C.L. Sibley, Pheasants (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - B.S. Jurale, Pheasants (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Charles Van Buren, Pheasants (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Vladimir Peter (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Physiology (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Plans, Poultry Farm (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Plans, Rice Hall, P.B. Building (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Plan of Development, Turkey and Duck Farm (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Plan of Development, Poultry Farm (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Plan of Development, Poultry Department (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Policy (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Committee, Poultry Science Teaching Award (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Poultry Science, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Poultry Science, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, Poultry Science Association Revised, July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Poultry Science, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Poultry Science, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Poultry Science, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Positions Wanted, 1957- (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Positions Available, 1957- (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Poultrymen's Get-Together, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Poultrymen's Get-Together, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Poultry Science Association Pamphlets, 7 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Poultry Science Awards (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Poultry Science, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Poultry Science, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Poultry Science, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Poultry Science, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Annual Mtg. Cornell University, Comments, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Poultry Science (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Poultry Science, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Poultry Science, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Poultry Science, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Poultry Science, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Poultry Science, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Poultry Science, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Poultry Science, 1947-1951 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Poultry Science, 1932-1946 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Poultry Farm Service Letter (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Programs, 1956- (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Q
    - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - R
    - Correspondence R, 1954- (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Radio, 1946- (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Reference Books and Publications, JHB, Aug. 28, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Research Projects, State 274-277 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Research Work in the Poultry Department (Stencil), Feb. 2, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Reprints (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Rice Memorial Library: Memos, Minutes, Progress Reports, and Statements of Committee, 1948- (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - John V.B. Rice, 1940- (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Rice Library, 1960- (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Rice Testimonial Fund Portrait (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Rice Testimonial Dinner (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dedication, Rice Hall (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Report, P.S.A. Meeting, Orino, Maine, Aug. 1911 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Rice Memorial Library: Corresponence, 1953-1959 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - A.L. Romanoff, 1929-1943 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - A.L. Ramanoff, 1944-1953 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - E.I. Robertson, 1940- (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - David Rodriquez, 1945- (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - S
    - Salmonella (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence S, 1954- (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Seminar, Poultry Biology, Spring 1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - H.M. Scott (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Schilling (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Seminars (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - W.E. Shaklee (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Charles Sibley, Conservation, Fernow Hall (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sigma Xi (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - S.P.C.A. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Society for the Study of Evolution (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Marshall F. Spear (See Long Island Duck Growers) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Staff (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Staff Directory, Oct. 16, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Staff, 1954-1963 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Staff, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Staff, 1937-1950 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - State Institutes, 1953- (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - State University (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - State University, Delhi, Agr. and Tech. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - State University, Faculty (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Statler Club, 1950- (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Paul D. Sturkie, 1942- (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Syracuse Sanitary Code, 1952- (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Nigel A. Sutcliffe (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - A.M. Syrigos, 1953- (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - T
    - Correspondence, 1954- (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Turkeys, 1954- (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Turkeys, 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Effron vs. The State of New York (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - C.N. Turner, 1949- (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - U
    - United Fund, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence U, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - V
    - Ari Van Tienhoven (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence V, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Frans Van Dooren, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Vineland Laboratories, 1957- (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - W
    - World's Poultry Congress, Constitution (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - L.E. Weaver, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - United Fund, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Ward (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence W, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - H.B. and R.B. Wallace, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - H.B. Wallace and R.B. Wallace, 1946-1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - L.E. Weaver, 1943-1953 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Willers, D.K. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - H.S. Wilgus, Jr., 1942- (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - John H. Williamson (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - X-Y
    - Correspondence X-Y, 1954- (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - R.J. Young (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Young (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Z
    - Correspondence Z (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Chester Zimmer, 1948- (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Personal files, A, G, H, T
  - A
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Alpha Gamma Rho, National (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Alpha Gamma Rho, Zeta Chapter (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Alpha Gamma Rho, Delta Chapter (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Alpha Zeta Fraternity (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - G
    - Game Farm (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Game Farm, Civil Service Exam (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - H
    - Everybody's Poultry Magazine, Dec. 1959; Sept. 1953,; May 1963 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - T
    - TIAA-CREF Annual Report, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Old correspondence, A-Z
  - A
    - V.S. Asmundson, 1944-1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - B
    - H.E. Botsford (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Robert F. Ball, 1942-1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Babcock's Hatchery, 1942-1951 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence B (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - H.E. Botsford, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Breeders Conference, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Max M. Brender, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - C
    - Chick Pointers, 1928; 1929 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - D
    - Danish Poultry Farm (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - G
    - Correspondence G (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - H
    - Correspondence H (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Hall Brothers Hatchery, 1941-1947 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Hall Brothers Hatchery, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Hogestt Poultry Ranch, 1940-1953 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - I
    - Incubation School (Poultry), July 1935 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence I (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - J
    - Correspondence J (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - L
    - Correspondence L (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Mac and Mc
    - Correspondence Mac and Mc (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - M
    - Massachusettes Breeders School (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - N
    - National Turkey Improvement Plan, 1943-1953 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council, 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Council, 1938-1945 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - N.Y.S. Baby Chick Association, 1941-1953 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - N.Y.S. Food Commission, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - N.Y.S. Poultry Association, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - O
    - R.C. Ogle, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence O (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - P
    - Poultry Breeder and Hatcheryman's School, Nov. 10-13, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Poultrymen's Get-Together, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Poultrymen's Get-Together, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - R
    - James E. Rice (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Alexis L. Romanoff (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - E.I. Robertson (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - R.E. Reynolds, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Rice Memorial Library Correspondence, A-J, 1948-1952 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Rice Memorial Library Correspondence, K-Z, 1948-1952 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - S
    - Correpondence S (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Statistics, Commercial Hatchery Report, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Statistics, Poultry, Egg and Hatchery Report, 1954- (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Statistics, Poultry, Egg and Hatchery Report, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Statistics, Poultry, Egg and Hatchery Report, 1944-1950 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Statistics, Poultry, and Egg Situation, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Hatchery Production Report, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Statistics, Livestock, Turkey, and Field Crops, 1942-1950 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Statistics, Production and Marketing (Misc.) (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Statistics, Turkey-Poultry Hatchery Report, 1951- (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Statistics, Neppco Boiler Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Statistics, Neppco Handbook, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Sterilamps, 1944-1947 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - SPICE, Extension Feed Co. Meeting for the NE Egg Production (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - T
    - T, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - W
    - W.P.A. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Western Egg Laying Contest, Financial Statements (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Wildlife Society (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Charles H. Weidner, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence W (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - X,Y,Z
    - Correspondence Y (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Z (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Additional correspondence ( 1964-1965 ), A-Z
  - Agway (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - A, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - B, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - C, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - D, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - E, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - F, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - G, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - H, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - John P. Hertel (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - I, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Inquiries (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - J, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - K, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - L, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - M, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - N, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - O, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - P, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Poultry Science (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Purdue University (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Q, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - R, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - S, 1964-2965 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - T, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Travel Vouchers, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - U, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - V, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - W, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - X,Y,Z, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Additional correspondence ( 1963 ), A-Z
  - A, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - B, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Bruckner's Travel Vouchers, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - C, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 42)